hi girls just wanted to who is this it's
Pinkie Pie how did you get our numbers
yeah we just changed them I didn't
change mine because I'm sexy and I'm
always ready to talk to my friends just
wanted to send you a quick reminder
about tonight's slumber party what
slumber party silly dashy we talked
about this all last week you promised
you'd come I don't remember you
trying to Gaslight us pinky dear
I'm terribly sorry but I simply cannot
attend I have a lot of work to do and
well slumber parties just aren't my
thing especially given that you're all
in your mid 20s and I'm going on 40 now
I really do need to get back to my
beauty rest but Rarity we plan this
together sorry pinky I don't we call oh
no my connection is breaking up can you
hear me pinky
I can hear you just fine
Applejack uh well I can't hear you got
to go now
bye Fluttershy I suppose I can come over
for a bit dashy damn it okay fine yippi
this is going to be the best sleepover
ever oh hi girls what brings you to
sugar cube Corner today maybe a root
beer float or blueberry pie and ice
cream you literally just called us over
dumbass Ponies are so cute yeah they are
so small I bet they out so much
poop He I forgot I'm such a silly clutz
hey now that you're here what do you
want to play well I did see this really
fun thing going around on horse talk
called the candy salad Challenge Horse
talk you mean that one app the mayor is
Banning from Ville this year claiming
it's some Canterlot spyware that's the
one candy salad is a thing where you get
a group of your friends together and one
by one you announce your name while
pouring your favorite candy into a bowl
and then you mix it up or we could and
this is going to sound crazy Twilight
just eat the candy
[Applause]
stop what would be the fun in that I
think it sounds fun yeah and afterwards
we can post it online and read all the
nice comments well me I guess just
my
life hello every pony I'm Twilight
Sparkle and these are my awesome friends
hi today sh up it's twilight I'm putting
you got frosting with that cake hey
Fluttershy you are filming the candy
right I'm Rainbow Dash and I'm putting
in Skittles aka the most awesomest candy
in the world skitt and it's got to be
the sour shut the up no CH you tell
them
rainbow I'm Pinkie Pie and I like
Smarties
Smarties hey move it back really
Smarties what's wrong with Smarties
they're delicious who the hell likes
Smarties I do l m a o this
stop I said stop don't let that
contaminate my Skittles you know this is
going on right so what Smarties are the
yummiest yummiest isn't even a word you
idiot ironic how her favorite candy are
Smarties when she obviously isn't a
smarty herself Buttershy are you
hearing this just so you know your
life so you might want to tone it down
with the language shut the up this
is a stupid game I'm just going to eat
my candy you got to put something in for
the video I don't want
to hi ever Pony I'm Pinkie Pie and I'm
putting in my favorite candy blueberry
moon pies moon pies are not candy yeah
they're graham crackers dipped in
chocolate with marshmallow what do you
want from me this is the only thing I
had in my cupboard we want you to put in
candy I just tried that a second ago and
you got mad at me put that back
down hi every pony I'm Pinkie Pie and
I'm done with this
we could always play another game
name pinky oh I know how about Truth or
Dare yeah I'm sure there's no way that
could go horribly wrong what do you say
p PE want to give it a whirl well okay
as long as you promise to take it easy
on me all right then Truth or Dare it is
so who goes first how about we go from
least to most so I can go first
hold up first we need to attach our
obedience colors what for if these
collars detect a lie they will zap you
with 2,000 watts of electricity it's the
only way to stop Pinkie Pie from
cheating do they work Pinkie Pie are you
racist um
no okay let's get this started since
this is my house I get to go first no we
get to go before you because you have a
room temperature IQ resulting in a dull
unintelligent mind um okay since I'm
such a good friend no we get to go first
because we were born normal this has
nothing to do with
friendship all right puppy pie Truth or
Dare truth pick something else dare I
dare you to stack three
blocks I dare you to stack three blocks
and make me scrambled eggs come on
Twilight stacking a couple toy blocks
that's a little lame don't you think
maybe for horses that aren't
but for a bastard child
like like her perfectly stacking three
blocks would be like one of us pooping
in a toilet and not
missing oh yeah just watch me we
are stop stop laughing at me you're
breaking my concentration that's that's
awfully cruel Twilight giving the
Pony a geometry
challenge yeah I thought it would be
funny because I expected the chances of
her being able to complete the Dare was
rather minimal come on why won't you
just stay up there just get up there get
up
there that's it I don't want to play
anymore Oh Come the on Pinky it's
all in good fun well I'm not laughing
you know I have a wide array of
Developmental delays and physical
disabilities caused by genetic disorder
so why do you always have to play these
stupid pranks on me they're really
disheartening especially when it comes
from my own gal Pals I could only
understand like half of that because
your lisp is so bad shees pinky it was
only a joke if you couldn't do it you
should have dropped out why do you have
to go and kill the mood when we're
having
fun are you sure you want to do this
scoots absolutely I need to know why
Rainbow Dash is having a sleepover
without inviting me we are like 3 years
old our bedtime is 4:00 in the
afternoon that doesn't matter Rainbow
Dash is my best
friend she farted you into a trash can
and left you for dead What's Happening
Now scoots it looks like they're playing
truth or dare see we can play Truth or
Dare too let's go to my house and ask
Rarity if we can have our own sleepover
I don't want to go to your house it
sucks and your sister is no fun she is
so remember when she made us popcorn she
didn't put butter on it uh
Sweetie Belle your eye fell out should
we go find Miss jerle and get you a
Band-Aid golly scoo I'm so sorry here
you can borrow mine
maybe you're right dashy you girls were
just having fun and being silly and and
if anyone knows silly it's good old
Pinkie poie wow you turned it from funny
to super cringey real
fast py I'm going to the kitchen for a
cupcake you girls can carry on Hey
if you're going downstairs get me
a cider yo Caked Up dump truck if you
want anything make it known now Pink's
going on a run for us I could go
for a cider an apple cider sounds
lovely okay Twilight now it's your turn
Truth or Dare truth what's the most
embarrassing moment of your life
[Music]
uh I don't
remember Pinkie
Pie I thought you could use a hoof with
the cider why are you under the
table me I was just looking for The
Cider haha it's in the fridge where it
always is of course how could I forget
pinky have you been crying crying who's
been crying we're having such a fun
night tonight let's hurry back to the
game oh well we kind of agreed on a new
game Fluttershy wants to play hide and
seek so we don't have to interact with
you hide and seek yay I love that game I
know the best hiding spots actually me
and the girls talked about it and we
came to an agreement that you should be
the one to count but why because since
you struggle to count to four it will
give us more time to look for hiding
spots as we are not familiar with your
home's layout know that this is not a
personal dig at you this is merely a
tactical strategy of my own construction
Okie doie Loki I'll count to 10 and then
I'll come find you 1 2 3 um 1 2 um
that'll buy us a good 45 minutes let's
scadaddle
you expect me to go out there in that
storm what if a lightning bolt shoots
down and zaps my Bodacious ass it's
certainly a big enough Target so is
Fluttershy but you don't hear her
complaining he he here I come girls I'm
going to find you damn it she counted
all the way to 10 but it's only been 45
minutes that's got to be a new record
our only chance now is to Brave the
storm every pony link Hooves so we don't
get lost in the Tempest are you sure we
should be doing this I mean she has been
looking forward to this sleepover all
week that girl has the mental capacity
of an actual
baby we'll give her a box of animal
crackers and she'll forget this night
ever happened damn that stinks girls
where are you I can't find you hey
what's that animal
crackers yummy what was I doing again
you too go on your own I'll hang back
and tell her you girls had to go home
because you got nauseous from her smelly
ass then you will suffer the unfortunate
consequences of being a good friend all
by yourself
godp speed you crazy
girls come on this isn't fun anymore I
don't like this let's do something else
please dashy I found you yeah it looks
like you did now you can help me find
the rest of our friends well I don't
exactly know how to tell you this but
the others all already went home oh my
God they went to pick me up a cake
literally nothing I said implied that
yeah you're right it's okay if you want
to leave too I know you weren't having
much fun tonight anyway I don't want you
to stay just because you feel bad for me
no way I'm here for you and besides it's
not a real sleepover without staying the
whole night right how about we go
upstairs to your room and watch some
movies just the two of us that sounds
super duper fun let's do it
you're barely even watching the movie do
you like the rain that much I like the
way it looks it's so pretty and calming
like the whole world is taking a nice
cool
shower you okay there oh I'm just peachy
just a little jumpy from the Thunder
that's all hey I get it storms can be
pretty scary sometimes I just don't want
you to think I'm a scary pony every pony
gets scared and besides you got the most
awesomest Pony in all of Ponyville by
your side tonight nothing can happen to
you while I'm around thanks dashy you
always know how to make me feel
better hey after the movie is over want
to go downstairs and make cupcakes yeah
the most super duper delicious cupcakes
ever what is wrong with me I'm the best
the fastest coolest most awesome Pony in
all of Equestria I deserve the best
someone just as cool and awesome as me
so why would I settle for such a dumb
girl like this it wouldn't make any
sense I wonder what the others would say
if such a thing ever happened they'd
probably laugh and say I'd lost my mind
or something it already sucks hearing
the sorts of things every pony says
about you behind your back although I
suppose I wasn't much better than them
last night was I I'm sure they'd start
saying the same about me but then
again should I even care what they think
I mean it doesn't bother you or maybe it
does is that why you go off on your own
so much to let it all
out sorry pinky I've been a
idiot I'll make it up to you soon maybe
we'll go on a trip to mainhattan or
something well I'm going to be on my way
thanks for the party it's been a blast
oh hey there's Princess Celestia raising
the sun Princess Celestia Princess
Celestia good morning personal slave
it's always a treat for you to be in my
vicinity I wanted to see the sunrise
with you it's been a while since I've
had the chance to witness it from here
hey do you think no you don't even know
what I was going to say you were going
to ask if you could help me raise the
Sun and as usual the answer is no you
might drop it on bon bon down there and
I personally don't think that pony would
like being turned into burnt toast I
guess that would be bad and then there's
the issue of coordination it takes years
of practice to raise the sun without
accidentally turning the sky neon green
neon green I thought the sky just turned
blue and orange during Sunrise usually
yes but one wrong move and you'll have a
neon green sky with pink PKA dots oh wow
also do you remember that time you
multiplied your library books and caused
them to fly around the room yeah I do
now imagine that with giant balls of
flaming gas yep I remember the time I
tried to teach Luna she managed to move
the Sun but she made it spin like a top
we had a disco Sun for an entire week I
read about that ancient historians call
it the great disco Sunrise of
Equestria yeah it was pretty bitching
until the sun fell down and killed over
80% of the living popul
causing civilization to start all over
again but I think we're doing just well
for ourselves here just to be nice I'll
let you hold the Sun for 5 seconds would
you like that my faithful student oh yes
[Music]
please nice Twilight you did exactly
what I told you not to do well you're
the one who put it in my mind I know you
didn't just talk back to me well there
goes Manhattan Twilight I am so going to
spank you after
and now the sky is turning green you've
really outdid yourself this morning you
know what just let me do it before
ponies go
extinct pinky pinky what are you doing
up here you know it's currently a legal
for Earth ponies to visit Cloudsdale
after the incident I came to see you do
you want to hang out we just spent the
whole night together don't you ever get
tired how can I be when there's always
so much fun to be had like watching ing
the sunrise with my best buddy I just
wish I could sit there with you but we
come from two different
worlds hey thank you for staying the
night with me it's no biggie what the
hell am I saying of course it was I am
pretty awesome aren't I super duper
awesome totally why can't the others see
it too like that one time I did that
double Loop to Loop twist in 10 seconds
flat absolutely you're the best flyer
ever no pony even comes close that's
what I'm always saying I'm the fastest
the coolest and most daring Pony to ever
live yeah you're the most amazing and
brave it's it's really inspiring thanks
that means a lot coming from you
you're so wacky and zany you make Crazy
Bread seem normal well it's easy to be
happy when I'm around you cuz I I do
love you a whole lot
what I know I'm not smart like Twilight
or strong like Apple Jack and I'm
nowhere near as kind as Fluttershy or
pretty as Rarity but I try my best
because you're special to me dashy I
really really do adore you
uh look pinky you're you're the best
friend any Pony could ask for but I
think you may be a little confused what
do you mean I know how I feel I know you
think you do sometimes ponies confuse
strong friendship for something more you
and I have always been close so maybe
that's what you're
feeling I get it having a pony like me
hanging around wouldn't look very good
with your
image after all I'm sure you die of
embarrassment being spotted with a
don't say that I'd never be
embarrassed by you I swear I'm not like
the others rainbow
you've always been the rainbow after my
[Music]
storm as long as you're happy pinky then
that makes me happy too
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
spee
fore
[Music]
for now